A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Press Materials FA1322
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Record Group 2, Accession 2018:088, 1953-2002; 2; 32.15 Cubic Feet 34 LTR size, 1 Half-LTR size, 40 LGL size, and 1 Half-LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - Press clippings, 1953-2002; 2; 21.9 Cubic Feet 10 LTR size, 38 LGL size, and 1 Half-LGL size Hollinger boxes
    - Office of Reports flap files, 1953-1974; 3; .62 Cubic Feet About 1 LTR size and .5 LGL size Hollinger boxes
      Subseries contains a small set of press clipping files created and maintained by the Ford Foundation Office of Reports. The Office of Reports labeled this material as flap files. Their content and description suggest that they were created to document the Office's public relations work. Press clippings were collected and used to inform public relations strategy, and memos and correspondence within the files provide evidence of how the Office of Reports assessed and responded to media commentary on the Foundation's operations. Effectively responding to press criticism appears to have been a key priority within the Office's public relations strategy.
      - Editorial and public relations - General, 1956-1970 (Box 36, Folder 911)
      - Editorial and public relations - General, 1955-1974 (Box 36, Folder 912)
      - Editorial and public relations - General, 1960-1964 (Box 37, Folder 913)
      - Editorial and public relations - General, 1953-1962 (Box 37, Folder 914)
      - Editorial and public relations - General, 1967-1970 (Box 37, Folder 915)
      - Editorial and public relations - General, 1965-1974 (Box 37, Folder 916)
      - Press criticism, 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 917)
      - Press criticism, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 918-919)
      - Press criticism, 1955-1969 (Box 37, Folder 920)
      - Press criticism, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 921)
    - Clippings, 1983-1998; 4; 13.16 Cubic Feet About 28 LGL size Hollinger boxes
      Subseries consists mostly of press clippings collected for the Ford Foundation by the Burrelle's and Luce press clipping services during the 1980s and 1990s. In addition to housing press clipping files created to document media coverage on particular Ford Foundation programs, the subseries also holds files created to document coverage published by individual newspapers and files created to document coverage on individual Foundation staff members.
      Furthermore, there are some files in the subseries that contain press logs. These logs document communication between the Ford Foundation and members of the press.
      - Ford Foundation staff - Investments, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 922)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Gary Sick, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 923)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Charles Silberman, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 924)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Franklin Thomas, 1984-1988 (Box 38, Folder 925-926)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Louis Winnick, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 927)
      - Ford Foundation staff, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 928)
      - Ford Foundation Trustees - Thomas Wyman, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 929)
      - Ford Foundation Trustees, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 930)
      - General press clippings, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 931)
      - General press clippings, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 932)
      - General press clippings, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 933)
      - General press clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 934)
      - General press clippings, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 935)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Housing, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 936)
      - Human Rights and Governance Program, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 937)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Teen parents, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 938)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Child care, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 939)
      - General press clippings, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 940)
      - Program Related Investments (PRI), 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 941)
      - AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 942)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 943-944)
      - Franklin A. Thomas and Ford Foundation Trustees, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 945)
      - General press clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 946)
      - General press clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 947)
      - General press clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 948)
      - Trustees trip, Franklin A. Thomas and Ford Foundation Trustees, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 949)
      - Student dropout program, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 950)
      - AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 951)
      - Rural Poverty Program/Developing Countries Program, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 952)
      - Governance and Public Policy Program (GPP), 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 953)
      - General press clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 954)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 955)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1983-1988 (Box 40, Folder 956)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 957)
      - Student testing, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 958)
      - National Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 959-960)
      - TV Log, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 961)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 April-July (Box 40, Folder 962-963)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 July (Box 40, Folder 964-965)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 July-August (Box 41, Folder 966)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992 January (Box 41, Folder 967)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992 February (Box 41, Folder 968)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992 March (Box 41, Folder 969)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992 June-July (Box 41, Folder 970)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992 August (Box 41, Folder 971)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992 April (Box 41, Folder 972)
      - Press logs, circa 1991 (Box 41, Folder 973)
      - Press logs, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 974)
      - Press logs, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 795)
      - Press logs, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 976)
      - Press logs, 1992 April (Box 41, Folder 977)
      - Press logs, 1990-1992 (Box 41, Folder 978)
      - Press logs, 1990-1992 (Box 41, Folder 979)
      - Press logs, 1990-1992 (Box 41, Folder 980)
      - General press clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 41, Folder 981)
      - General press clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 982)
      - Press release - Ford and MacArthur Foundations grants to community foundations, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 983-984)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1991 December (Box 42, Folder 985)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 January (Box 42, Folder 986)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 February (Box 42, Folder 987)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 January-March (Box 42, Folder 988-989)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 March-April (Box 42, Folder 990-991)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992 May (Box 42, Folder 992-993)
      - Major articles, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 994)
      - Luce Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 995)
      - Circulated press clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 996)
      - Relinking Life and Work: Toward a Better Future, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 997)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 998)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 999)
      - General press clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 1000-1003)
      - General press clippings, 1998 March-August (Box 44, Folder 1004-1006)
      - General press clippings, 1998 July-October (Box 44, Folder 1007-1008)
      - Grants made, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 1009)
      - Anti-Ford Foundation press, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 1010)
      - Ford Foundation staff and building, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 1011-1012)
      - Ford Foundation President Susan Berresford, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 1013)
      - Events, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1014)
      - Obituaries, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1015-1016)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 1017)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program (PSJ), Governance and Civil Society (GCS), 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 1018)
      - Other foundations and philanthropy, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 1019-1020)
      - Lily Endowment, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 1021-1022)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Community and Resource Development, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 1023)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Economic Development, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 1024)
      - Weirton Daily Times loose clipping - State center will help women with home-based businesses, 1998 February 12 (Box 46, Folder 1025)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 1026)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Education, Knowledge and Religion (EKR), 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 1027-1028)
      - Rural Community College Initiative, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 1029)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Media, Arts and Culture (MAC), 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 1030-1031)
      - Multiple programs and Ford Foundation mentions, 1998 March-August (Box 47, Folder 1032-1039)
      - Multiple programs and Ford Foundation mentions, 1998 March-May (Box 48, Folder 1040-1042)
      - Multiple programs and Ford Foundation mentions, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 1043-1046)
      - Columns, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 1047-1048)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program (RPR), 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1049-1051)
      - Press release - Adult Literacy Media Project, 1991-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1052-1053)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1054-1055)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Martin Luther King exhibition, "Countdown to Eternity", 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1056)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Community development and neighborhood revitalization, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1057)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Discrimination in workplace survey, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 1058)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Domestic violence, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1059)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Gambling survey, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1060-1061)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Housing, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1062)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Parents/families, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1063)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Quantum opportunities, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1064)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Violence prevention, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1065)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Welfare reform, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1066)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Youth Service America and AmeriCorps, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1067)
      - Regional - Asia Programs, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1068)
      - Regional - Africa and Middle East Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1069)
      - Regional - Latin America Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1070)
      - Ford Foundation staff and Trustees, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1071-1073)
      - Administration, building, and general press clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 1074)
      - Publications - Announcements and reviews, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 1075)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Community and Resource Development, 1998 July-December (Box 51, Folder 1076)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Economic Development, 1998 July-December (Box 51, Folder 1077)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 1998 July-December (Box 51, Folder 1078-1079)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) - Copies, 1998 May-September (Box 51, Folder 1080)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), 1998 July-December (Box 51, Folder 1081-1082)
      - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture Program (EMAC), Education, Knowledge and Religion (EKR), 1998 July-December (Box 51, Folder 1083-1084)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), 1998 July-December (Box 52, Folder 1085-1087)
      - Peace and Social Justice Program (PSJ), Governance and Civil Society (GCS), 1998 July-December (Box 52, Folder 1088)
      - Campus diversity in higher education, 1998 August-December (Box 52, Folder 1089-1091)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program - 1998 award winners, 1998 June-November (Box 52, Folder 1092)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program - 1998 semifinalists and finalists, 1998 May-November (Box 52, Folder 1093-1094)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program, 1998 May-November (Box 52, Folder 1095-1096)
      - Innovations in American Government Awards Program - Previous year award winners, 1998 June-November (Box 52, Folder 1097)
      - Community Development Corporations (CDCs), 1998 December (Box 52, Folder 1098)
      - Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) - Low income mortgages, 1998 July-December (Box 53, Folder 1099-1100)
      - Rural Community College Initiative, 1998 August-November (Box 53, Folder 1101)
      - General press clippings, 1998 November-December (Box 53, Folder 1102-1104)
      - General press clippings, 1998 November (Box 53, Folder 1105-1107)
      - General press clippings, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 1108-1110)
      - General press clippings, 1998 September (Box 54, Folder 1111)
      - Ford Foundation mention - Rob Fondaw, 1998 August 20 (Box 54, Folder 1112)
      - Ford Foundation grants and scholarships, 1998 October-November (Box 54, Folder 1113)
      - Ford Foundation staff and Trustees, 1998 July-December (Box 54, Folder 1114)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 January (Box 54, Folder 1115)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 February (Box 54, Folder 1116)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 March (Box 54, Folder 1117)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 March-April (Box 54, Folder 1118)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 May (Box 54, Folder 1119)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 June (Box 54, Folder 1120)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 July (Box 54, Folder 1121)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992 August (Box 54, Folder 1122)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1991 December 31 (Box 54, Folder 1123)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 January (Box 54, Folder 1124)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 February (Box 54, Folder 1125)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 March (Box 54, Folder 1126)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 April (Box 54, Folder 1127)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 May (Box 54, Folder 1128)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 June (Box 54, Folder 1129)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 1130)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992 August (Box 55, Folder 1131)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1991 December 29 (Box 55, Folder 1132)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 January (Box 55, Folder 1133)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 February (Box 55, Folder 1134)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 March (Box 55, Folder 1135)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 April (Box 55, Folder 1136)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 May (Box 55, Folder 1137-1138)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 June (Box 55, Folder 1139-1140)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 1141)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 August (Box 55, Folder 1142)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992 September (Box 55, Folder 1143)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1991 October (Box 55, Folder 1144)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 January (Box 55, Folder 1145)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 February (Box 55, Folder 1146)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 March (Box 55, Folder 1147)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 April (Box 55, Folder 1148)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 May (Box 55, Folder 1149)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 June (Box 55, Folder 1150)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 1151)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992 August-September (Box 55, Folder 1152)
      - Ford Foundation staff, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 1153-1154)
      - Program Related Investments (PRI), 1992 July (Box 56, Folder 1155)
      - General press clippings, 1992 January (Box 56, Folder 1156)
      - General press clippings, 1992 February (Box 56, Folder 1157)
      - General press clippings, 1992 March (Box 56, Folder 1158)
      - General press clippings, 1992 April (Box 56, Folder 1159)
      - General press clippings, 1992 May (Box 56, Folder 1160)
      - General press clippings, 1992 June (Box 56, Folder 1161-1162)
      - General press clippings, 1992 July (Box 56, Folder 1163)
      - General press clippings, 1992 August (Box 56, Folder 1164)
      - General press clippings, 1992 Sepember (Box 56, Folder 1165)
      - Governance and Public Policy Program (GPP), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1166-1167)
      - Governance and Public Policy Program (GPP) - Common Ground for the Common Good, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1168)
      - Governance and Public Policy Program (GPP) - Sidney Verba report, Citizen Participation Project, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1169)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 1170)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program - 1993 award winners (Box 57, Folder 1171-1172)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1173-1174)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1175-1177)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1178)
      - International Affairs Program (IA), 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1179)
      - International Affairs Program (IA) - United Nations Financing Report, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1180)
      - International Affairs Program (IA) - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1181)
      - Media Projects Program, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1182)
      - Program Related Investments (PRI), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 1183)
      - Urban Poverty Program, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1184-1189)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Housing report, Joint Center for Housing Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1190-1191)
      - Urban Poverty Program - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC), 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1192)
      - Reproductive Health and Population Program (RHP), 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1193-1194)
      - Reproductive Health and Population Program (RHP) - Pharmaceutical research, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1195)
      - Reproductive Health and Population Program (RHP) - AIDS/HIV, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1196)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ), 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1197-1198)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ) - Women's programs, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1199)
      - Rights and Social Justice Program (RSJ) - Political asylum study project, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1200)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1201-1203)
      - Rural Poverty and Resources Program - Water crisis study, Last Oaisis: Facing Water Scarcity, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1204-1205)
      - Civil War Miniseries - PBS Video, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 1206)
        File does not contain any press clippings. Contents include newsletters, a memo, and a purchase order related to the order of two sets of the PBS Civil War Miniseries.
      - Public relations services, 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1207)
        File does not contain any press clippings. Contents concern Jones and Associates Communications, a public relations services firm that sought to do work with the Ford Foundation.
      - Ford Foundation staff and Trustees, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 1208)
      - Ford Foundation staff - An-Na'im, Abdullahi A., 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1209)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Beckham, Edgar, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1210)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Bernstein, Alison, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1211)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Carson, Emmett, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1212)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Cohen, Stephen, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1213)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Coward, E. Walter, 1992 October 29 (Box 60, Folder 1214)
      - Ford Foundation staff - English, John, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1215)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Gerhart, John, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1216)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Hatton, Barbara, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1217)
      - Ford Foundation Trustee - Jordan, Vernon, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1218)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Kennedy, Roger, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1219)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Lipsky, Michael, 1993 July (Box 60, Folder 1220)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Lowry, W. McNeil, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1221)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Schull, Joseph, 1993 July 5 (Box 60, Folder 1222)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Strumpf, Linda, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1223)
      - Ford Foundation President - Thomas, Franklin A., 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1224)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Urquhart, Brian, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1225)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Walker, Lynn, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1226)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Zeitlin, June, 1993 June 21 (Box 60, Folder 1227)
      - Ford Foundation staff - Zwerling, L.S. (Steve), 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1228)
      - Ford Foundation staff and Trustees, A-H, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1229)
      - Ford Foundation staff and Trustees, I-P, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1230)
      - Ford Foundation staff and Trustees, Q-Z, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1231)
      - Administration - Grant announcements, 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1232)
      - Administration - Harry Nugent (subway conductor), 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1233)
      - Administration, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1234-1235)
      - Administration - Kevin Roche (and Associates), 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1236)
      - Administration - Ford Foundation sponsored books and publications, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1237)
      - Education and Culture Program, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1238-1246)
      - Education and Culture Program - National Minorities in Higher Education Program, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 1247)
      - Education and Culture Program - Break Away, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1248)
      - Education and Culture Program - Hispanic internships and other items, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 1249)
      - Education and Culture Program - Community colleges, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 1250)
      - Education and Culture Program - Campus diversity, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 1251)
      - Education and Culture Program - Bill Clinton's National Service Plan, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1252)
      - Education and Culture Program - Teachers and school reform, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1253)
      - Education and Culture Program - Witness for Freedom book, Black Abolitionists Papers Project, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 1254)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program press releases - 1992 semifinalists (Box 62, Folder 1255)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program press releases - 1992 finalists, undated (Box 62, Folder 1256)
      - Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program press releases - 1992 winners, undated (Box 62, Folder 1257)